{
    "subject": "resource/Laugh_Now,_Cry_Later",
    "predicate": "property/extra",
    "object": "Lil Jon",
    "human_readable": "The extra of Laugh Now, Cry Later is Lil Jon.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9531815052032471,
            "question": "Is Lil Jon a featured artist on 'Laugh Now, Cry Later'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9088169932365417,
            "question": "Besides 'Laugh Now, Cry Later', what are some other popular songs by Lil Jon?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8326377272605896,
            "question": "Which artist collaborated with Lil Jon for the track 'Laugh Now, Cry Later'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8318425416946411,
            "question": "What role does Lil Jon play in the song 'Laugh Now, Cry Later'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8200143575668335,
            "question": "What makes the collaboration between Lil Jon and the artist on 'Laugh Now, Cry Later' unique?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8143906593322754,
            "question": "Who is featured on the extra of the song 'Laugh Now, Cry Later'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.732959508895874,
            "question": "What song features Lil Jon as an extra?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6616804003715515,
            "question": "Name the track that includes Lil Jon as an extra."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.38251256942749023,
            "question": "Aside from being a rapper, what other role does Lil Jon have in music?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3376484811306,
            "question": "What genre of music is associated with Lil Jon?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The extra of Laugh Now, Cry Later is Lil Jon.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3415_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Aside from being a rapper, what other role does Lil Jon have in music?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3415_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Name the track that includes Lil Jon as an extra.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3415_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What song features Lil Jon as an extra?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3415_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3415_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3415_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3415_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3415_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3415_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3415_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3415_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3415_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3415_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3415_7.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'no'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The provided context does not mention Lil Jon as a collaborator for the song \"Laugh Now Cry Later.\" It mentions Lil Durk as the featured artist. Therefore, the statement that the extra (collaborator) of \"Laugh Now Cry Later\" is Lil Jon is incorrect based on the given information."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"no\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "mistral": {
            "reason": "There is no information provided in the context indicating that Lil Jon was part of \"Laugh Now, Cry Later.\" Collaborations mentioned include Snoop Dogg and Lil Durk for Ice Cube's version, and it is Drake and Lil Durk for the more recent version.",
            "category": 4
        },
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "It states Lil Jon is featured on the song, but the provided context lists Snoop Dogg as a collaborator on Ice Cube's album with the same name. It also says Lil Durk is featured on Drake's \"Laugh Now Cry Later\".",
            "category": 4
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "The extra of \"Laugh Now Cry Later\" is actually Lil Durk, not Lil Jon.",
            "category": 4
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "reason": "The context information mentions that \"Laugh Now Cry Later\" was collaborated with Lil Durk, not Lil Jon.",
            "category": 4
        }
    }
}